James A. Pike Papers
James A. Pike Papers
- Writings by others
  - Fisher, Geoffrey Francis, Address before 55th Protestant Episcopal Church, 1946; published material (Box 106)
  - Fleming, Thomas J., "Can Protestants and Catholics Ever Get Together?", 1961; published material (Box 106)
  - Forbes, Anthony H., "Religious Studies--Dual Loyalty: The Roman Catholic Dilemma under the Early Stuarts", 1967; published material (Box 106)
  - Fosbroke, Hughell E.W., "Divine Transcendence in the Old Testament", 1950; published material (Box 106)
  - Fuller, H. Reginald, "On Demythologizing the Trinity", 1961; published material (Box 106)
  - Geppert, David, "Transcript of Ouija Board Sessions", 1965; typescript (Box 106)
  - Guild of St. Ives, "Report on Churches and Taxation", May 1967; typescript repro (Box 106)
  - Hansen, Ben, "The Two-Child Family Movement: A Creative Approach to World Peace", 1966; typescript repro (Box 106)
  - Heaton, Lee W., The Churchman, May 3, 1924-Jun 21, 1924; Dec 26, 1925; published material (Box 106)
  - Hedley, George, "The Liturgical Movement in Methodism", 1963; typescript copy (Box 106)
  - Hedley, George, "Worship: Principles and Practice", 1964; typescript copy (Box 106)
  - Hoffman, Harry Lee, "Old Wine In A New Bottle", 1964; typescript copy (Box 106)
  - Holt, Ivan Lee, "Approaches to Inter-Communion", 1955; published material (Box 106)
  - Holt, Ivan Lee, "A Plan for A United Church in the United States", 1953; published material (Box 106)
  - Huron, George, "The Pope", 1966; page proofs (Box 107)
  - Joint Department on Religious Liberty, National Council of Churches, "The Things Most Surely Believed Among Us", typescript repro (Box 107)
  - Jones, Harry W., Annual Riverside Lecture, 1956; typescript copy (Box 107)
  - Kelsey, P.M., The Heart of Those Who Soar, 1970; printed material (Box 107)
  - Kenrick, Mari, miscellaneous comments on ancient religion, 1966; typescript annotated (Box 107)
  - Kinsolving, Lester, "The Bishop's Not for Burning" Ramparts, Jan 1967; published material (Box 107)
  - Lea, William, "Is the Bishop Above the Law?" Episcopal Churchnews, 1956(?); typescript copy annotated (Box 107)
  - Lutheran Church, Missouri Synod, Report of Commission On Theology and Church Relations, 1968; repro. (Box 107)
  - Macquarrie, John, "A Look at the New Theology", 1967; printed material (Box 107)
  - McDonald, D., "Essays In Our Day", 1966; typescript reproduction (Box 107)
  - Mooney, Kathryn M., ''Orthodoxy Revisited (or) Our Roots and Our Wings", 1958; typescript (Box 107)
  - Moore, Francis John, "Eating the Flesh and Drinking the Blood", 1966; printed material (Box 107)
  - Morris, Frederick, "Can We Talk With The Dead?", 1967(?); published material (Box 107)
  - Morris, John, ed., "New Ways With the Ministry", 1960; published material (Box 107)
  - Murray, John Courtney, "The Freedom of Man in the Freedom of the Church", 1957; published material (Box 107)
  - Outler, Albert C., "Iconoclasm and the Integrity of the Faith", 1968(?); typescript reproduction (Box 107)
  - Pike, Diane Kennedy, 1969-1972; New Focus newsletters, copy of her book Search (Box 107)
  - Pike, Esther, "Who Is My Neighbor?", typescript carbon (Box 107)
  - Polier, Justine Wise, "Israel's 'Law of Return'", 1959; typescript copy (Box 107)
  - Population explosion, subject file of clippings, etc by others on the topic (Box 107)
  - Pusey, Nathan M. and Hines, John E., "Ministry for Tomorrow", published material (Box 107, Box 86)
  - Rainwater, Lee, "...And the Poor Get Children", 1960(?); book manuscript (Box 107)
  - Richards, Michael, "Liverpool Metropolitan Cathedral of Christ the King", 1953; published material (Box 108)
  - Rienhardt, Kurt F., "Scientist-Humanist Dialogue", 1967; published material (Box 108)
  - Scott, Michael, "Report on Hyasaland--The Cholo Affair", typescript copy (Box 108)
  - Sherman, Jonathan Goodhue, "The Spirit of Knowledge", 1961; published material (Box 108)
  - Skinner, John E., "The American Death of God Theology", 1967; published material (Box 108)
  - Smith, Ronald Gregor, "A Theological Perspective of The Secular", 1960; published material (Box 108)
  - Solomon, Joseph C., "Alice and the Red King--The Psycho-Analytic View of Existence", 1963; published material (Box 108)
  - Stringfellow, William and Towne, Anthony, The Bishop Pike Affair, Harper & Row, 1966; unbound proofs, notes, legal agreements, correspondence, etc. (Box 108)
  - Theology and advertising, subject file of clippings, etc by others on the topic (Box 108)
  - Tilbrook, Gilmore Lee, "Rythmeter", 1954(?); printed material (Box 108)
  - Tillich, Paul, "Theology of Education", 1956; typescript copy (Box 108)
  - Tittmann, George, 1963; printed material (Box 108)
    Typescripts of five articles: Atheism, Indispensible Enemy; The Causes of Disbelief; Basic Thoughts About Faith; Exploring the Holy Trinity
  - Trueblood, Elton, "The Continued Education of Ministers, ", 1955; printed material (Box 108)
  - VanDusen, John G., "Morningside Heights, Inc.", 1954; dissertation typescript (Box 108)
  - VanKirk, Agnes E., "The Church -- Her Purpose: The Extension of the Incarnation", 1939; published material (Box 108)
  - vanLeeuwen, Arend Theodoor, "Prophecy in a Technocratic Era--Part I", 1965; printed material (Box 109)
  - VonRohr, John, "Toward a Theology of Homosexuality", 1969; typescript reproduction (Box 109)
  - West, Edwin E., Sermon preached at the Church of the Redeemer, Palo Alto, California, 1962; reproduction (Box 109)
  - White, Lynn, Jr., "The Historical Roots of our Ecologic Crisis" Science, 1967; article reprint (Box 109)
  - Wilcox, J., "Law and Ethics Term Paper", 1967; typescript (Box 109)
  - [Unknown], "The Paradox of the Diaconate", typescript annotated (Box 109)
  - [Unknown], Statement on the Office of the Bishop, draft A, holograph; draft B, typescript revised; draft C, typescript copy revised (Box 109)
  - [Unknown], photocopy of part of unidentified book (Box 109)
Selected index to correspondence
All correspondence is incoming (to Pike), unless noted as "(outgoing)".
Adler, Mortimer J. May 18 1966
Allegro, John Marco Feb 24 1966 to May 7 1968
Altizer, Thomas J.J. Aug 24 1967
Ashmore, Harry C. Jul 1 1966 to Jul 6 1966 Jul 18 1969 Jul 19 1969
Auden, W.H. May 8 1955 to May 13 1955
Baggs, William C. May 12 1966 to Jun 19 1966 Sep 21 1966
Barnes, Hazel E. Oct 30 1967
Barnes, Roswell P. Jan 14 1949 to Jan 24 1949 to Jan 27 1955
Beaman, Robert Apr 27 1958 to May 1 1958
Beker, J. Christiaan May 11 1968 to May 15 1968
Bennett, John C. Nov 29 1954 Mar 18 1955 to Apr 15 1955 Feb 5 1956 to Feb 7 1956 Jan 1 1957 to Jan 16 1957 Jun 25 1964 to Nov 9 1966 Nov 16 1966 Dec 9 1966 to Feb 2 1967
Bently, Eric Feb 6 1961 to Feb 16 1961
Berrigan, Daniel Sep 10 1968 to Sep 19 1968
Berthold, Fred Dec 14 1956 to Jan 10 1957 Nov 14 1957 Dec 28 1957
Blach, Charles Dec 31 1957 (outgoing)
Blake, Eugene Carson Oct 22 1956 to Oct 25 1960
Blanding, Sarah Gibson Oct 8 1948 (outgoing) Nov 25 1948 to Dec 1 1948 to Apr 5 1949 Apr 13 1949 May 2 1949 to Sep 12 1949 Sep 15 1949 Dec 2 1949 to Dec 9 1949 Jun 9 1950 to Aug 15 1950 Sep 13 1950
Blanshard, Paul Feb 10 1957 to Aug 6 1957
Blanton, Smiley May 14 1953 to May 18 1953 Mar 14 1957 to Mar 18 1957 Jan 22 1965 to Feb 2 1965
Bliss, Kathleen Feb 25 1955 (outgoing)
Block, Marguerite Feb 21 1954 to Feb 26 1954
Bonnell, John Sutherland Feb 26 1958 to Mar 2 1958 to Dec 9 1967 Dec 27 1967
Bowye, Walter Russell Jan 17 1949 to Jan 20 1949
Boyd, Malcolm Aug 18 1967
Branscomb, Harvie Mar 2 1953 to Mar 11 1953 Mar 16 1953
Bretall, Robert W. Feb 3 1967
Brown, Edmund G. Dec 3 1958 May 2 1960 Sep 8 1966
Brown, F. Craighill Jan 4 1950 (outgoing) Jan 13 1950 Feb 13 1953 Feb 19 1953 to Mar 20 1953 Mar 26 1953 Apr ? 1953 to Apr 11 1953 May 4 1953 May 13 1953 May 21 1953 May 30 1953 to Jun 4 1953 Feb 10 1958 to Feb 13 1958
Brown, Robert McAfee Feb 23 1953 to Mar 3 1953
Bunche, Ralph Jan 18 1957 to Jan 24 1957
Burton, Phillip Aug 1 1966
Cailliet, Emile Apr 27 1955 to May 2 1955
Canfield, Cass Sep 10 1957 to Sep 16 1957 Nov 3 1966
Case, Clifford P. Feb 15 1957 to Feb 19 1957
Cassels, Louis Nov 7 1966
Cavert, Samuel McCrea Feb 20 1956 to Mar 7 1956 Mar 9 1956 to Mar 13 1956 Jun 28 1960 to Aug 22 1960
Chamberlin, Laurence H. Jan 30 1952 Feb 13 1953 to Feb 16 1953 Feb 27 1953 to Dec 31 1957 Jan 3 1958
Cherbonnier, E. LaB. Sep 26 1955 to Oct 3 1955 to Apr 11 1958
Clebsch, William A. Nov 2 1936 to Nov 13 1956 to Nov 27 1964 Nov 30 1964
Coburn, John Bowen Jan 9 1959 to Mar 16 1959 Mar 30 1959 Nov 2 1959 to Nov 5 1959 to Jun 15 1960 Apr 17 1961 to Apr 19 1961 Nov 23 1966 to Dec 27 1966 to Jun 25 1968 Jul 16 1969
Cousins, Norman Dec 8 1959 (outgoing) Sep 13 1965
Cranston, Alan Sep 12 1966
Crowther, C. G. Jul 9 1965
Culley, Margaret Sep 3 1965
Daly, John C. Feb 6 1958 to Feb 11 1958
Davis, Elmer May 16 1955
Davis, Thurston Feb 1 1958 (outgoing) Feb 5 1958 Apr 17 1958 to Apr 25 1958 to Nov 2 1962
Demant, V. Auguste Feb 23 1955 (outgoing) Mar 6 1955
DeMille, Cecil B. Dec 29 1956
Dewart, Leslie Sep 20 1967 to Dec 29 1967
Dickey, John Sloan Aug 1 1956 Sep 17 1956 Nov 5 1956 to Jan 2 1957 to Mar 12 1957
Dillenberger, John Mar 11 1952 to Nov 20 1956 Dec 20 1966 to Jun 27 1967
Dillistone, F. W. Apr 13 1952
DuBay, William H. Aug 28 1967 to Sep 6 1967 Sep 6 1967
Duke, Angier Biddle Sep 10 1957
Dun, Angus Dec 26 1950 Nov 5 1951 mar 23 1954 to Mar 30 1954 Apr 1954
Eisendrath, Maurice N. Apr 30 1965 to May 4 1965 May 7 1965 Jul 22 1965 to Aug 13 1965
Eisenhower, Dwight D. Nov ? 1956 (outgoing) Nov 16 1956 to Nov 23 1956 to Jan 18 1957
Eliot, T.S. Feb 25 1955 (outgoing) Mar 2 1955
Ernst, Morris L. Mar 26 1956 to Mar 29 1956 Dec 12 1958 to Dec 17 1958 Nov 26 1965
Exman, Eugene Mar 7 1955 Jun 1 1955 to Jun 6 1955 to Jun 23 1955 May 11 1960 to May 17 1960 Jun 3 1960 Mar 13 1951 to Dec 14 1951 Dec 19 1953 to Jun 7 1960 to Jun 9 1960 Jun 24 1960 to Jun 27 1960 Nov 13 1961 to Nov 17 1961 to Jan 19 1962 Jan 24 1962 Jul 3 1962 Jul 17 1962 to Jul 24 1962 to Sep 18 1962 to Mar 4 1963 to Feb 14 1964 to Feb 19 1964 to Jul 25 1968 Feb 4 1969 to Feb 11 1969
Famula, Sister Mary Nov 12 1966 Dec 25 1966
Ferre, Nels F. S. Mar 1 1969
Fey, Harold L. 1957 to Dec 10 1957
Fletcher, Joseph May 13 1954 to May 17 1954 May 11 1956 to May 14 1956 Jun 21 1956
Fosdick, Harry Emerson Oct 21 1955 to Oct 24 1955
Frankfurter, Felix Dec 10 1940
Fromm, Erich Jun 13 1957 Oct 23 1957 to Nov 11 1957 Nov 22 1957 to Nov 29 1957
Fuller, Reginald H. Apr 23 1965 to May 23 1965
Gallagher, Buell G. Feb 11 1958 to Feb 26 1958
Giambastini, J. F. Aug 30 1968 to Sep 25 1968
Gilpatric, Roswell L. Dec 11 1959 (outgoing)
Goldstein, Israel Oct 5 1955
Graham, Billy Feb 10 1958 to Feb 19 1958
Grant, Frederick C. Jan 10 1949 to Jan 14 1949 Mar 13 1951 to Dec 14 1951 Dec 19 1951 to Mar 29 1954 Feb 5 1958 ? ? 1964 Sep 2 1964 Sep 2 1964 to Sep 8 1964 Sep 23 1964 Mar 24 1967 Jul 24 1967
Grant, Robert M. Feb 19 1953 to Feb 24 1953
Grennan, Jacqueline Feb 28 1967 to Mar 16 1967
Gunther, John Jun 24 1957 Oct 4 1957
Hacker, Louis B. Feb 16 1953 to Feb 19 1953 Aug 15 1957
Hamilton, William Oct 30 1966
Hammerstein, Oscar Dec 20 1954 Jan 30 1935
Handy, Edward A. May 1 1952 to Jun 9 1952
Harriman, W. Averell Mar 12 1956 to Dec 4 1957 (outgoing)
Harrington, Donald Oct 21 1955 to Nov 3 1955 Feb 6 1958
Hazelton, Roger Jul 29 1955 to Aug 15 1955
Heckscher, August Feb 12 1958 to Feb 19 1958
Hennings, Thomas B. Jr.(Senator) Aug 16 1955 (outgoing) May 27 1955 to Jan 28 1955
Henry, Carl F.H. Dec 22 1966 (outgoing)
Henry, Leland B. Jan 28 1948 Feb 3 1949 ? ? 1952 Jan 21 1953 Feb 23 1953 Jun 15 1955 to Jun 28 1955 to Apr 17 1957 Oct 4 1966 Oct 11 1966 to Oct 18 1966 Dec 2 1966
Hicks, R. Lansing Dec 19 1952 to Jan 10 1953 Apr 9 1953 May 1953 to May 27 1953 Aug 14 1953 Nov 16 1966
Hiltner, Seward Jan 11 1954 to Jan 15 1954 Feb 13 1954
Hines, John E. (Bishop) Aug 31 1965
Hocking, William Ernest Oct 23 1951 to Oct 29 1951
Hodgson, Leonard Feb 26 1957 to Mar 19 1957
Hooft, W. A. Visser't Oct 23 1956 to Oct 29 1956
Hook, Sidney Jun 17 1957 (outgoing)
Hoon, Paul W. Feb 9 1955
Houlihan, John Sep 21 1966
Horton, Douglas May 21 1966 to Jul 13 1966
Howe, Reuel L. Jan 3 1958 to Jan 9 1958 to Jan 31 1958
Humphrey, Hubert H. Jan 22 1957
Hurst, Fannie Mar 8 1958 to Mar 10 1958
Hutchins, Robert M. Jan 11 1957 (outgoing) Mar 7 1958 to Mar 15 1958 to Arp 12 1966 Apr 19 1966
Illich, Ivan D. Apr 1964
Irion, Paul T. Apr 15 1967 to Oct 11 1967
Javits, Jacob K. Feb 10 1958 to Feb 17 1958 Sep 10 1958 to Sep 25 1958
Johnson, Howard A. Feb 29 1952 to Mar 11 1952 Jan 26 1953 Feb 13 1953 Feb 19 1953 Mar ? 1953 Mar 5 1953 Mar 30 1953 to Nov 20 1953 Nov 23 1953 to Nov 30 1953 Dec 5 1953 to Jan 4 1954 Jan 19 1954 to Jan 30 1954 Feb 7 1954 to Feb 15 1954 to Feb 16 1954 Feb 20 1954 to Mar 2 1954 Mar 26 1954 Apr 3 1954 to Apr 8 1954 Apr 30 1954 May 1954 to May 21 1954 Jun 2 1954 Jun 30 1954 Feb 1955 Feb 10 1958 to Feb 12 1958 Sep 5 1958 to Jan 9 1959 to Apr 30 1959 May 5 1959 to Aug 20 1959 to Aug 21 1959 Aug 24 1959 Sep 15 1959 to Sep 29 1959 to Jun 8 1962 Jun 13 1962 to Feb 18 1964 Mar 2 1964
Johnson, Lyndon Baines Feb 23 1965
Johnson, Sherman E. May 6 1957 (outgoing) May 9 1957 to May 15 1957 to Apr 29 1958 Sep 16 1965 Nov 14 1967
Kavanaugh, James J. May 8 1968 to May 10 1968
Kazan, Elia Jan 18 1957 to Jan 20 1957 May 21 1957
King, Martin Luther Jan 8 1957 to Jan 10 1957 to Sep 9 1966 to Jun 15 1967 to Jul 12 1967 Jul 17 1967 to Jul 20 1967 to Aug 11 1967
Kirk, Grayson Jan 11 1952 (outgoing) Jan 18 1952 Feb 7 1958 to Feb 10 1958 to Feb 14 1958
Kissinger, Henry A. Dec 29 1956 Jan 17 1957
Knight, Goodwin Feb 6 1958 to Feb 11 1958
Knox, John Feb 27 1946 Oct 2 1956 Feb 18 1957 to Feb 28 1957 Feb 7 1958 to Feb 27 1958
Krumm, John M. Dec 29 1950 (outgoing) Feb 20 1951 Nov 7 1951 to Nov 14 1951 Feb 6 1958 to Feb 11 1958 Feb 21 1958 to Feb 28 1958 to Jun 12 1962 Jun 14 1962 to Jun 22 1962 Jun 25 1962 Oct 7 1966 Jul 11 1967 to Jul 27 1967 to Jun 19 1969
Kuchel, Thomas H. Sep 8 1966 to Oct 11 1967
Langer, William Feb 16 1954 (outgoing)
Lasky, Victor Mar 29 1954
Lilienthal, David E. May 22 1953 to May 30 1953
Lowrie, Walter ? ? 1950 (outgoing) Oct 21 1950 Mar 23 1955 May 6 1957 to May 10 1957
Lowry, Charles Wesley Mar 25 1954 to Mar 26 1954 Sep 29 1954 Nov 17 1957 to Nov 27 1957 to Dec 10 1957
Luce, Clare Booth Mar 26 1958
Luce, Henry R. Dec 1 1961 (outgoing) Dec 21 1961 Dec 23 1961 to Dec 29 1961 to Jan 16 1962 Jan 19 1962 to Jan 30 1962 Dec 28 1964
MacCleod, George Aug 20 1966
MacGregor, Geddes Jul 29 1954 to Aug 2 1954 Jan 21 1957 Oct 4 1957 to Oct 9 1957 Apr 7 1965
MacIntyre, Alasdair Aug 14 1968 (outgoing)
MacIver, Robert M. Jan 4 1957 to Jan 12 1957 Feb 5 1957 to Feb 23 1957
MacKay, John A. Mar 7 1958 to Mar 11 1958
Macquarrie, John Jul 6 1967 (outgoing) Jul 10 1967
McCarthy, Eugene J. Sep 13 1968 (outgoing) Nov 21 1968
McCracken, Robert J. Feb 6 1958 to Feb 17 1958
McGill, Ralph E. Jan 31 1961 Sep 2 1965 Nov 21 1966
McGucken, Joseph T. Sep 12 1966
McIntire, Carl Dec 2 1966 to Dec 15 1966
McLaughlin, John Jul 3 1967 to Jul 27 1967
McNair, Robert M. Feb 14 1953 Jul ? 1953 to Jul 22 1953 Oct ? 1966 to Oct 18 1966
Means, Cyril C., Jr. Apr 9 1956 Apr 27 1956 Apr 29 1956 May 1 1956 Oct 23 1957 to Nov 1 1957 Feb 5 1958 Feb 17 1958 Jun 4 1958 to Jun 7 1958 Oct 23 1966 Feb 14 1967 to Ftb 24 1967
Menninger, Karl Oct 20 1953 to Nov 9 1953 Nov 12 1953 Mar 5 1957 to Mar 20 1957 Mar 4 1958 to Mar 20 1958
Metcalf, George R. Apr 3 1957 to Apr 8 1957
Michalis, C. G. Jul 22 1951
Miller, Randolph Crump Mar 24 1958 to Mar 31 1958 Dec 4 1966 Nov 7 1967 Apr 15 1968 to Jul 16 1968
Mondale, Walter F. Jan 10 1968 to Mar 12 1968 Mar 23 1968
Montefiore, Hugh Jan 18 1965 to Feb 3 1965 Feb 10 1965 Apr 20 1965 to Apr 26 1965 Aug 11 1966 to Sep 9 1966 Sep 14 1966 Dec 2 1968 Dec 16 1968
Moore, Paul Apr 21 1953 (outgoing)
Moreau, Jules L. Oct 3 1966 to Oct 18 1966 Dec 7 1966
Morris, Frederick M. Mar 25 1968 (outgoing) Mar 29 1968
Morse, Wayne Jun 5 1967 to Jun 13 1967
Mosk, Richard M. Nov 4 1966
Moyers, William D. Aug 17 1967 to Aug 25 1967 Aug 30 1967 to Sep 11 1967
Muste, A.J. Mar 5 1953 to Mar 11 1953 Apr 29 1955 to May 2 1955 Oct 15 1956 to Oct 24 1956 Nov 1 1956 to Nov 7 1956 Apr 1 1957 to Apr 3 1957
Niebuhr, Reinhold Jan 13 1952 Feb 11 1952 to Feb 13 1952 to Jul 23 1954 Mar 22 1955 Feb 5 1958 Feb 12 1958 to Feb 14 1958 to Feb 25 1958
Niebuhr, Richard R. Nov 2 1952 to Nov 5 1952 Oct 15 1957 to Oct 28 1957
Niebuhr, Ursala Mar 15 1949 to Mar 17 1949 to Apr 22 1954 to Oct 2 1961 Nov 26 1966
Nineham, D.E. Jun 25 1965 (outgoing) Jul 1 1965 Jul 12 1965
Nixon, Richard M. Jun 24 1958
O'Dwyer, Paul Feb 13 1953
Outler, Albert C. Apr 11 1957 (outgoing)
Overstreet, Harry A. Aug 14 1952 Aug 23 1952 Aug 28 1952 to Oct 31 1953
Oxnam, G. Bromley Jun 1 1954
Paar, Jack May 7 1958 (outgoing)
Parker, Pierson Sep 6 1965
Peale, Norman Vincent Jan 9 1956 to Jan 11 1956 Feb 7 1958
Pfeffer, Leo Oct 27 1954 to Oct 29 1954 Nov 19 1956 to Nov 21 1956 Feb 7 1958 to Feb 19 1958 Aug 14 1961 to Aug 16 1961
Pike, Catherine Dec 30 1965
Pike, Christopher Jun ? 1967?
Pike, Esther ? ? 1964
Pittenger, W. Norman undated Nov ? 1950 Jul 16 1951 Jan 28 1952 to Feb 18 1952 May 31 1952 to Jun 16 1952 Jun 17 1952 Aug 8 1952 Aug 18 1952 to Aug 21 1952 May 8 1957 Nov 7 1957 to Nov 18 1957 Feb 5 1958
Poage, W. R. Jun 20 1957 to Jul 17 1957 Jul 19 1957
Polier, Justine Wise Nov 8 1955 Oct 1 1957
Polier, Shad Nov 2 1955 Jan 6 1956 to Jan 11 1956 May 31 1956 Jan 31 1957 Feb 25 1957 Feb 28 1957 to Mar 1 1957 Mar 5 1957 Mar 6 1957 to Mar 11 1957 Mar 12 1957 to Mar 18 1957 Mar 28 1957 to Apr 3 1957 Apr 22 1957 to Jun 19 1957 Jul 26 1957 Sep 16 1957 Sep 17 1957 to Sep 24 1957 Oct 4 1957 to Oct 8 1957 Nov 6 1957 to Nov 14 1957 Nov 25 1957 Nov 29 1957 Dec 4 1957 Feb 6 1958 to Feb 13 1958
Poling, Daniel A. Jan 18 1960 to Jan 22 1960 Mar 16 1960 to Mar 28 1960 Nov 16 1960 Nov 21 1960 to Dec 2 1960 Dec 28 1960 to Jan 6 1961
Pollard, William G. Feb 17 1954 (outgoing) Feb 19 1954 Mar 23 1954 to Apr 21 1954 to May 13 1955 May 17 1955 to May 20 1955 Aug 30 1957
Pollock, Thomas Clark Nov 1 1951 Jul 9 1955 to Jul 20 1955
Pusey, Nathan M. Jun 14 1950
Rahner, Karl Jun 13 1966 (outgoing)
Ramsey, R. Paul Jun 1955 to Jun 7 1955 to Jun 13 1955
Rathbone, Basil Jun 23 1954 (outgoing) Jun 26 1954
Reston, James B. Apr 8 1954 (outgoing) Apr 3 1954
Reuther, Victor Feb 5 1957
Reuther, Walter Nov 11 1957 to Nov 29 1957
Richardson, Cyril C. Mar 29 1954 to Apr 3 1954 Jan ? 1955 to Jan 20 1955 Mar 1 1955 to Mar 7 1955 Feb 13 1958 to Feb 22 1958
Ridgeway, Matthew B. Jun 30 1953 to Jul 6 1953
Ritschl, Dietrich Apr 10 1967 to Apr 28 1967
Robinson, James H. Jul 7 1965 to Jul 3 1967
Robinson, John A.T. Jun 12 1964 Aug 13 1965 Dec 5 1966 Dec 8 1966
Rockefeller, Nelson A. Oct 31 1956 to Nov 2 1956
Roosevelt, Eleanor Apr 25 1957 to Apr 29 1957 Apr 30 1957 to Apr 9 1958 to Apr 10 1958 Apr 15 1958
Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr. Feb 16 1953 to Feb 17 1953
Rostow, Eugene V. Jul 5 1955 Feb 7 1958 to Feb 13 1958
Roy, Ralph Lord Oct 18 1953 to Oct 20 1953 Feb 23 1956 to Feb 27 1956
Ruether, Rosemary 1968 to Nov 26 1968
Rustin, Bayard Oct 24 1956 to Oct 26 1956
Rylaarsdam, J. Coert May 21 1957 to May 27 1957
Sarnoff, Robert W. Jan 18 1961 to Jan 23 1961
Sayre, Francis B. Jun 25 1953 to Jun 30 1953 Apr 15 1958 to Apr 20 1958 May 14 1959 Nov 14 1959
Scott, G. Michael Jan 25 1954 Mar 4 1954 to Mar 5 1954 to Mar 23 1954 to Apr 21 1954 Jul 12 1954 to Jul 28 1954 Feb 6 1955 Feb 14 1955 to Feb 28 1955 Nov 19 1957
Scribner, Charles Jr. May 3 1966 to Jul 6 1966
Shephard, Massey H. Feb 14 1958 to Oct 7 1958 Mar 9 1963 May 23 1966 to Jul 15 1966 Jun 13 1967 Jun 14 1967 to Jun 28 1967 to Jan 16 1968 Jan 20 1968 Oct 16 1968 to Oct 30 1968 Mar 17 1969 to Mar 28 1969
Shriver, Robert Sargent Jun 6 1952 to Jun 10 1952 Jun 30 1952
Simcox, Carrol E. Feb 11 1965 to Mar 1 1965 Nov 18 1966 to NoV 23 1966
Smith, H. Alexander Mar 18 1955 to Mar 29 1955 Apr 12 1955
Smith, Margaret Chase Jan 16 1957 to Jan 21 1957
Spellman, Francis Cardinal Dec 18 1951
Sockman, Ralph W. Apr 1 1957 (outgoing) Jun 10 1957 Feb 7 1958 to Feb 19 1958
Soe, N. H. Dec 31 1954 (outgoing)
Spurrier, William A. May 24 1955
Stinnette, Charles R. Jan 19 1953 to Jan 10 1953
Stringfellow, William ? ? 1966 Oct 26 1966 Oct 26 1966 Mar 10 1967 Aug ? 1967
Swift, Arthur L. Nov 10 1955 to Nov 25 1955
Tavard, George H. Feb 10 1958 to Feb 18 1958
Thomas, Lowell Nov 4 1955 (outgoing) Nov 18 1955 to Nov 21 1955
Thomas, Norman Apr 7 1954 Jan 17 1957 to Jan 24 1957 Nov 17 1959
Tillich, Hannah (Mrs. Paul) Nov 3 1968 to Nov 27 1968
Towne, Anthony Sep 13 1968 to Sep 19 1968
Trilling, Lionel Mar 8, 1958 to Mar 11 1958
Trueblood, Elton Mar 21 1955 (outgoing)
Van Buren, Abigail Jun 24 1967
Van Duse, Henry P. Dec 31 1952 (outgoing) Dec 1 1957 to Dec 6 1957 Mar 25 1958 to Mar 31 1958
Vidler, Alexander R. Jun 29 1965 (outgoing)
Visser t'Hooft, W.A. Oct 23 1956 to Oct 29 1956
Wagner, Robert F. Sep 19 1957 (outgoing) Dec 4 1957 Feb 13 1958 to Feb 22 1958 Apr 23 1955 to May 15 1958
Walsh, Chad Feb 28 1953 to Mar 11 1953 Mar 11 1953 to Nov 2 1953 Jan 26 1954
Watts, Alan W. Mar 25 1965
Webber, George W. Mar 27 1969 (outgoing)
Wedel, Theodore Sep 24 1943 (outgoing) Jan 17 1949 to Jan 20 1949 Mar 31 1949 Apr 10 1953 Jan 5 1957 Feb 3 1957 to Feb 7 1957 Feb 5 1958
Wencelius, Leon Jan 9 1965
Wheeler, Harvey Sep 13 1966
Wright, Richard Feb 10 1949 to Feb 7 1949
Zabriskie, Alexander C. Jun 1 1951 Nov 21 1951 to Aug 15 1952 Jul 15 1953 to Aug 6 1953 Feb 18 1955 to Feb 21 1955 Feb 28 1955 to Mar 4 1955